Angemeldet bleiben   [Registrieren](https://bs.to/registrierung)

Navigation

* Favoriten
* Mehr

Privacy Policy
--------------

#### Effective date: April 1, 2019

Burning Series ("us", "we", or "our") operates the website accessible at **bs.to**, **burningseries.co**, including the App (each hereinafter referred to as the "Service") for which we are acting as a data controller with respect to the personal data of its users.  
  
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and service users and therefore we implemented numerous technical and organisational measures to ensure the most complete protection of personal data processed through this website. However, Internet-based data transmissions may in principle have security gaps, so absolute protection may not be guaranteed.  
  
By using the Service, **you agree** to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### 1\. Definitions

This policy and its data protection declaration is based on the terms used by the European legislator for the adoption of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Below we define and explain the terminology we use to ensure this privacy policy declaration is eligible and understandable.

* **Personal data**
    
    Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ("data subject"). An identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online id or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.
    
* **Data subject**
    
    Data subject is any identified or identifiable natural person, whose personal data is processed by the controller responsible for the processing.
    
* **Controller**
    
    Controller or controller responsible for the processing is the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data.
    
* **Processor**
    
    Processor is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller.
    
* **Processing**
    
    Processing is any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.
    
* **Third party**
    
    Third party is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the data subject, controller, processor and persons who, under the direct authority of the controller or processor, are authorised to process personal data.
    
* **Consent**
    
    Consent of the data subject is any freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous indication of the data subject's wishes by which he or she, by a statement or by a clear affirmative action, signifies agreement to the processing of personal data relating to him or her.

### 2\. Cookies

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser on your device. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. These cookies can be used for tracking purposes and/or to hold any information. This information typically does not personally identifiy a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. We use cookies for the following purposes:

* For authentication - required by our security system to work correctly
* For status - to determine whether you are logged in with your personal account
* For personalisation - like preferred website language
* For analysis - to analyse the use and performance of our website and its Service
* For advertising - to personalize and track the display of advertising

### 3\. Third party links

We may include links to third party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third party sites and are not responsible for their privacy statements.

### 4\. Data Collection and Use

* We may process data about your use of our website and services ("usage data"). This information is **de-personalized** and **anonymised**, unless we have your consent to not do so. The usage data may include your IP address, coarse geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. This usage data may be processed by us and/or Third party for the purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. This data is needed to deliver the content of our website correctly, optimize the content of our website and advertisement and to ensure the long-term viability of our information technology systems and website technology.
* We may process ("personal data") which may include a username and your e-mail address. This is only the case when you decide to register a user account with us. This information is **not** being shared with third party and we **do not** associate the personal data with the usage data.

### 5\. Data Security and Retention

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to only those persons who need to know. After the expiration of the retention period, which determines how long personal data is going to be stored, the corresponding information is routinely deleted, as long as it is no longer necessary for the fulfilment of the Service or the initiation of using our Service.

### 6\. International Transfer

Since we operate outside the European Economic Area (**EEA**), this could involve transferring your data outside the EEA or the origin of where your data is collected. Some of our external third parties are based outside the EEA too, so their processing of your data will also involve a transfer of data outside the EEA. Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring the provider is either part of the Privacy Shield or its country have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission.

### 7\. Legal basis for the processing

We may process personal data if it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party, for example, when processing operations are necessary for the supply of goods or to provide any other service, which is covered by Article 6(1) lit. b GDPR. Personal data may also be processed if we obtain consent for a specific purpose as stated in Article 6(1) lit. a GDPR. Processing operations which are not covered by any of the above mentioned legal grounds are based on legitimate interest. Legitimate interest means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent).

### 8\. Rights of the data subject

* **The right to access** your personal data. This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
* **The right to rectification** of personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.
* **The right to erasure** personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is _no good reason_ for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law.
* **The right to restrict processing** your personal data in the following scenarios:
    * If you want us to establish the data's accuracy.
    * Where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it.
    * Where we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of processing, but they are required by the data subject.
    * You have objected the use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.
* **The right to object to processing** of your personal data, if there is something about your particular situation which makes you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. We then shall no longer process the personal data in the event of the objection, unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject, or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
* **The right to data portability** by requesting a transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use.
* **The right to withdraw consent** where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.

### 9\. Amendments

We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website. Such updates are immediately effective when they are posted on this page. We may notify you of changes to this policy by e-mail or through the private messaging system on our website, but you are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

### 10\. Data protection officer

If you have any concerns or questions about our use of your personal data, you can contact our Data Protection Officer through the private messaging system on our website ([bs.to](https://bs.to/)) by sending a message to one of the [Team members](https://bs.to/team).

* © 2024 Burning Series™Version 1.1.8
